hey everyone welcome back to the channel
today we're going to talk about the
going away of business cards
not sure so here's a new thing that's
coming out with cole pupple p-o-p-l
today we're going to talk about the ins
the outs the pros the cons the
downloadable app the ease of it so stay
tuned
[Music]
hey everyone welcome back to the channel
so today we're going to talk about the
popple
and the wristband and the
back of the uh circle for the back of
your phone or leaving it out like that
so i already have the popo wristband
what you needed to do and what i did
ahead of time was i went and downloaded
the app i ordered it online
while it was getting sent to my house i
downloaded the app started going through
the app and i started it there's a lot
of stuff inside of the app that is very
very um
intricate with knowing your brand
putting things in there um you can't do
it on a computer so you got to do it on
your phone and there was images that i
wanted to use that were not on my phone
so
take the time to go through the app and
set it all up prior to getting your
package in the mail it's so much more
easy and it's very very very beneficial
when it comes to that so pay attention
to that so when it comes to the app
opening up the app look through all the
stuff in there you're going to edit the
profile you're going to add some things
in here you're going to take away
there's going to be some things that you
want to do you're going to have to know
your instagram exact url
um link so what i did was on my computer
is i went and put um instagram.com came
up my profile copied paste and then put
it into an email my facebook link also
my linkedin link also and i also did
that and i sent them all to my phone
then i was able to copy and paste from
there inside of the app all the way back
and it worked out really really good
what i do love is the customizable
barcode that i'm going to show you right
there
you can put your little logo down in the
front it customizes it really really
good you can send it on emails
you could do a whole bunch of stuff when
it and stuff like that but what i wanted
for is i want to be at a wedding and i
don't want to have to fudge around with
trying to find a business card because i
always have 20 in my pocket at all times
most people don't so to put your wrist
out and have somebody tap it with their
phone that's just going to be game
changing so jen i'm going to go through
a couple of things we're going to do an
opening box and we're going to take a
look at it and we'll go from there so
stay tuned all right so what i did now
is we're going to do a top down from the
top and this is i already have the
the black one already on i've already
got it located the only thing you can't
do is activate it until you get it so
what it comes with
is the
box is going to come through here um
there's a little i didn't do the white
one yet on purpose because i wanted to
do it in front of you guys um
do that right inside of there
slide that right out of there a little
information right there it's gonna slide
out like that we're gonna put this aside
i'm gonna put the box aside um this was
i found like the easiest part of it once
you get to the rest of the part
um the app is the most intricate part
once you activate this it it's a piece
of cake it's already set up and you'll
see why in just a minute so we're going
to put that out to the side this is
something i also ordered for the back of
my phone they have the larger circles
four inch in diameter and i wasn't sure
how i wanted to approach that if i was
going to do it any other way
and what my plan was i've got a bridal
show coming up this weekend so the plan
is to be able to utilize this um from
there so there's that so it looks like
it's just got
adhesive
to there to hold it together so we're
gonna put this back inside of here and
slap that back over there so this is
your popple um you can
customize these you can put your logo
across the top you can make them
different colors um i just wanted to
keep it simple for this fact for the
fact of it just just keeping it simple
and just do what it's purposely meant to
do
these you cannot customize they all come
with the papa logo on it but this over
here you can have this taken off you
could put your logo across your name tag
line anything like that i think those
are 29.99 but i'm not sure i'll put a
link in the description below to the
website from there so this came out
really good so i'm really looking
forward to all of this so now all right
so now we've got this i'm going to pull
up my phone
and i am going to add
this to the back of my phone it's going
to fit perfect that's exactly what i was
hoping for was going to fit right in the
back side of that so i'm going to put my
phone face down
i'm going to use my
shirt
to clean the surface i recommend you do
something else a little bit better than
that um but we're going to peel that i
got to activate this first so let's do
this so you're going to go into your
popple app which i put mine on my home
screen right in the back over there so
that's going to be opening up from there
so inside of the popple app you'll see
um how this all works inside of here so
let's do this we'll do all of this right
here so now we're going to do this so
edit profile um add
add links contact informational edit
profile details from here job
description uh your location job title
um
company um bio
change your colors across here like this
um change your links and icons if you
want to do that over here so if i want
to click on what it looks like in the
preview
we're going to go back into that
all right
all right edit so here's where you're
going to load these up over here so
you're going to put it in the website
text instagram if you want to move the
locations of them you see the three dots
on the side just like that you're going
to end up holding that and then you can
adjust whatever
order that you want them to go in and
then as you swipe up for me i have i
want people to go to my website text
instagram email as a last resort on my
youtube channel
and then i have a testimony that i have
and then my facebook which i have turned
off so all of these are turned on the
other apps that i have i have turned off
they're all in there they're all ready
to go but they're just turned off
because i don't want everybody to i'd
rather have people go to my instagram
then my facebook page i'd rather people
text me then go to so and they don't
need my venmo unless they're ready to
pay me so
if i did want it to go i'll have
somebody call me i can take this and i
can slide this right up to the top and
then turn that little icon on and it's
on so as of right now um everything is
good with that so here's the connection
so if i want to add a connections build
your network by scanning a business card
you can do that also and this is the
share part this is your popple app
if you want to edit it or create it it's
all inside of here i created that little
logo inside of the middle because that's
part of who i am the insights can tell
you who people you've been connected
with how many times you've opened the
pop link taps new connections uh and so
on and so forth but under settings over
here you want to activate a pop-up
device so once you open up that from
there you're going to see there's too
much of a glare on that or not but
you're going to click on the popple disk
and then
begin activation what you're going to do
is um it's going to tell you what to do
at the very top right here you're going
to take the popple
right there all i did was go right to
the back of it like that and it says
activate this device okay ready to scan
all right you have successfully
activated your pupple click okay okay so
now got it so now i can go back to uh
this is my name that's inside i can buy
another one if i want to do that from
inside of here we're back over here
we're going to also activate the other
bracelet so i have a black bracelet
that's already activated i need to begin
activation for let's go back a little
bit
cancel
okay i want to go back because now i got
to pick a different item to activate so
activate part of the device you're going
to click on the wristband right there
and then begin activation
and then watch what this does
take this
right across the back
and then right into the back
begin activation
ready to scan
you have successfully activated your
band okay so from there now if i want to
go back i want to shut my phone off i
want to be all the way back to here so
that same very bracelet that i just
activated if somebody comes up and taps
my wrist with it um this is what i'm
going to do
it's going to go like that
and then right there pulls up all of my
information when it comes to that so all
my information right there the website's
the first thing i want thing to go to
whatever you want people to contact you
or relate to you or get to you first
that's what you want first and you can
highlight them and you can adjust them
so i want website first i want them to
go there i want them to see my work if
they like that text call instagram email
and youtube and down here is a little
video that i created and that's all
inside of there so once this comes up a
little things gonna come over here
connect with me and then it's already me
so it's not going to connect to me
that's my website
so connect with me if i click on that my
information is going to come up in their
phone they're going to say add to your
contacts you click yes and they're all
set to go so that's the simplicity part
of that part so on the phone that's how
that whole thing works it's very very
simple when it comes to that and i like
that part of it uh and apparently my
light went out in the back over there um
that's the part that i like about it so
i've got it right there on my home
screen right there at the top anybody
that walks up they're going to walk up
to my phone they're going to click on
that bang just tap it and there it is
right there add me to your list and add
me to your contacts so take a look at
that right there so it's focusing on my
eye that's a sony a600 that i'm
recording with so that's what it looks
like when it comes to that so
that part's all set um
i did notice that you have to pull down
you have to pull down so i have an
android so
you have to pull this down and pull this
down again and over here you have to
make sure that your um
nfc ncf is on
so that might be something and it told
me the first time that it was not on so
i had to do um once i'm back out of here
again just want to show you again
there's the bracelet right to the back
there's your information connect with me
done your information gets added right
to there some people don't like i don't
want you in my contacts and that's okay
but i just wanted to show you um the
next level of
um business card philosophy i have
business cards and i'm still going to
carry business cards i put them down at
restaurants i put them down on boaster
boards when i'm at restaurants and
things like that sometimes if i'm
feeling ambition i'll put it i'll pay
when i'm done paying at the restaurant
i'll slip a little business card inside
of there because you just never know so
with that being said that's my review on
an open box of the popple i love the
philosophy behind it i like everything
about it so now i've got a white and a
black which i bought together and you
can buy two blacks two whites one black
one white um and then you can buy the
circle on there also and i wanted to
start with this because i've got the
bridal show coming up this weekend so
all i can say is thank you guys for
coming back to the channel greatly
appreciate it i'm trying to do videos on
things that i have that connected to me
and related to me
which is very important to me i'm trying
not to do things that are outside of the
realm of what i do i'm going to stay
authentic to who i am so thank you guys
for coming back to the channel do me a
favor hit that like button hit that
subscribe and hit that bell for
notifications uh and thank you for
coming back to the channel i've got the
quote for the day for you is not only do
we have to pursue purpose
we have to be patient in the process so
remember that when we're going through
things thank you for coming back to the
channel hit that subscribe button hit
that like button and hit that bell for
notifications and remember smile more it
hurts less peace
you